你想用什么颜色啊?
What color would you like to be?
呃 我想选绿的啊 可每次都被你选了
Well, I'd like to be green, but you know you always take it.
才不是咧
That's not true.
我用什么颜色都可以的啊
Any color's fine with me.
我可以用 蓝色和黄色混合起来的颜色
Yeah, I could be a combination of blue and yellow.
蓝色混黄色就是绿色
Blue and yellow make green.
那就这么愉快的决定了
Well, then it's settled.
嗨 准备好出发了吗
Hi. Ready to go?
哦 告诉你们一个好消息 我们订了午餐外卖
Oh, good news, we ordered lunch,
所以我们就能待在这玩指环王冒险了
so we can all stay here and play Lord of the Rings Risk.
Sheldon 我们不是说晚上才陪你玩游戏吗
Sheldon, we said that we would play games with you tonight.
哦 不 我们晚上还是在玩啊...
Oh, no, we'll still be playing it tonight...
这游戏很容易就玩上八小时的
this game can easily take eight hours.
亲爱的 你真的觉得我们想这样做啊?
Sweetie, you really thought I'd want to do this?
- 不啊  - 那你有告诉他吗?
- No.  - Well, did you tell him that?
- 有啊  - 你有大声的说出来告诉他吗?
- Yes.  - Did you say it out loud with words?
没
No.
我可不想花一整天时间去玩桌游
I don't want to spend the whole day playing a board game.
呃 当你们听到这是全新的拓展版本
Yeah, well, you may change your mind when you hear
里面有更完整的中洲的地图
that this is the new expanded edition
还包含了哈拉德地区
which contains a more complete map of Middle Earth,
你们可能就会改变主意了
now including the Haradwaith Territories.
咱俩比一比 看谁先跑回车上去
I will literally race you to the car.
不 不 不 拜托 别走嘛 来试试啊
No, no, no, come on, don't leave. Just try it.
不 我们一直都照你们男生想要的去做
No. We're always doing what you guys want.
就一次 要是你们照我们想要的去做就好了
Just once, it'd be nice if you did something we wanted.
你想用绿色吗?
You want to be green?
你要知道 他们真的有试着去喜欢
You know, they really have tried to like
我们爱玩的的东西了
a lot of the same stuff we're into.
是啊 我们陪你们打游戏 打电子游戏 看电影
Yeah, we do game nights and video game nights and we watch movies
还是有导演评论音轨的电影
with director's commentary.
我可得说说... 乔治卢卡斯
Oh, my favorite... George Lucas can talk
想怎么说星球大战就怎么说 我说一个字
all the way through Star Wars, I say one word
就被驱逐到厨房去了
and I'm banished to the kitchen.
是啊 今天Amy和我
Yeah, today Amy and I are deciding
决定我们所有人要做的事
what we're all gonna do.
行啊 今天你们女生说了算
You got it, you girls are in charge.
- 谢谢  - Sheldon?
- Thank you.  - Sheldon?
好吧
Fine.
现在我们不玩了 你可以选绿色了
Now that we're not playing, you can be green.
- 谢谢啊  - 既然这次你用绿色
- Thank you.  - And since you're green
下次就轮到我了
this time, I can be it next time.
好吧 我想想 有什么有趣的活动
All right, let's see. What's something fun
男人们永远不会带我们去做的?
the guys would never take us to do?
哦 我知道了... 我们可以去骑马
Oh, I know... we could go horseback riding.
我不行的
I actually can't.
我的臀部没法展开超过二十二度
My hips don't open wider than 22 degrees.
我骑过一匹很瘦小的
I rode a very thin pony once.
就颠了那么一下... 我就掉下来了
On the first bump... just popped right off.
好吧 呃 那你想干什么?
All right, well, what do you want to do?
在Wilshire有个手工艺民间艺术博物馆
There's a craft and folk art museum on Wilshire.
让Wilshire去管就好了
Well, that's Wilshire's problem.
拜托 肯定会有一些事
Come on, you know, there... there's
是我们觉得有趣而男人们讨厌的
got to be something fun we could do that the guys will hate.
等一下 为什么一定要是我们讨厌的啊?
Hang on, why do we have to hate it?
六个字 神秘博士展会
Three words: Doctor Who convention.
我 我没有强迫你去啊
I... I did not force you to go to that.
你戴着土耳其毡帽和蝴蝶领结就出门了
You walked out of the house in a fez and bow tie.
我跟着去是确保你不会挨揍
I went so you didn't get beat up.
我才不会挨揍呢
I wasn't gonna get beat up.
本来是要的 不知怎的我竟然忍住没打
You were, but somehow I held myself back.
你知道你能让我们做什么吗? 滑冰
You know what you could make us do? Ice-skating.
冰冷的空气会让Leonard的哮喘发作
The cold air will trigger Leonard's asthma
还正好碰上了我害怕的事
and it plays right into my well-known fear of
被磨冰机磨平
getting flattened by a Zamboni.
现在你是在帮她们想怎样让我们悲剧吗?
Now you're helping them find ways to make us miserable?
抱歉 Leonard 哥生下来就是为了解决问题的
Well, I'm sorry, Leonard, I'm a problem-solver, it's what I do.
我不能去滑冰的
I actually can't go ice-skating.
我有一双超级易碎的脚踝
I have unnaturally brittle ankles.
你身上还有哪个部位是正常的不?
Is there any part of your body that's normal?
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state  *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第八季十二集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影子
时间轴: 。沫
翻译: 柱君  猫呗  Astral  凤梨酥
校对: UU2222222了
我的天 我的天 我的天
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
- 你消停一会行不行?  - 我受不了了 兄弟
- Will you please relax?  - I can't take it, dude.
- 你没事吧?  - 不 我有事 我觉得
- You okay?  - No, I'm not okay. I feel like
内心火烧火燎的
I'm gonna jump out of my skin.
我跟你说了不要把下面的毛给脱了
I told you not to wax down there.
再长出来的时候会很痒的
It's itchy when it grows back.
我在担心新视野号空间探测器
I'm worried about the New Horizons space probe.
他在说什么啊?
What's he talking about?
九年前他是那个发射航天器
Nine years ago he was part of a team
到冥王星收集数据的项目团队中的一员
that launched a spacecraft to collect data about Pluto.
航天器终于够接近目标了
It's finally close enough, so
所以今天早上它自动启动了
this morning it turned itself on.
希望它启动了
We hope.
信号要走三十亿英里
The signal has to travel over three billion miles.
所以要等上好几小时我们才知道它是不是还完好
So it's gonna be hours before we know if it even survived.
现在我们看到他这么紧张是因为他担心
Now we get to see him flip out because he's worried
航天器会被太空冰块摧毁
it was demolished by space ice.
太空冰块一点都不好笑
Space ice is no joke.
我都不敢看冰雪奇缘了
I can't even watch Frozen anymore.
哦 交响乐团在市中心演奏贝多芬的曲子
Ooh, the philharmonic is playing Beethoven downtown.
呃 好吧 在你说同意之前
Yeah, well, before you say yes,
"贝多芬"也是一部宠物系列电影
这不是那部关于大狗狗的电影
it's not the movie about the big dog.
我们怎么会想不到一件我们都想做的事呢?
How come we can't think of something we both want to do?
因为我们要去做什么 决定权总在你
Because you always pick what we do
我只是跟着你去做罢了
and I just go along with it.
啊 有意思...
Ah, interesting...
你说我们强迫你们去做你不喜欢的事情
We're being accused of making you do things
然而你却对可怜的Amy
you don't like, and here you are,
做同样的事
doing the same thing to poor Amy.
你应该指出这样很虚伪
You should point out the hypocrisy of that.
我刚才不就是这个意思吗
That's what I was doing.
哦 你说的还不够清楚
Oh, that wasn't clear.
再试一次 这次直白点让她理解
Try it again, but this time drive it home
比如 "这样你满意了吗 小姐?"
with, "How do you like them apples, missy?"
好了 继续想
All right, keep thinking.
你把事情搞复杂了
You're making it too complicated.
为什么不从最基本的来?
Why not stick to the basics?
去逛街买衣服
Go shopping for clothes
然后Leonard和我守着你们的包包
while Leonard and I sit in those
坐在那些一点都不舒服的椅子上等着 嗯哼?
uncomfortable chairs and hold your purses, hmm?
我知道我讨厌这样
I know I'd hate that.
Leonard你呢?
Leonard?
嗯 也讨厌
Well, yeah.
好的 那么 就这么定了?
Well, then, it's settled?
你觉得怎么样? 听起来挺不错
What do you say? Sounds kind of perfect.
是不错... 但是让他这么一说
It does... somehow he managed
似乎把其中乐趣都说没了
to take all the fun out of it.
好了 再说一遍 哥就是干这行的
Well, once again, it's what I do.
还有两小时要等
Oh, another two hours to go.
这么等把我急死了
The wait is killing me.
我知道 我懂 我在联盟号太空船
I know. I get it. When I was in the Soyuz capsule
从国际空间站返回 以每小时17000英里
returning from the space station, plummeting toward Earth
- 直坠地球之时...  - 先问你一句
- at 17,000 miles per hour...  - Before you finish,
你这故事是有关耐心和等待
is this a story about patience and waiting
还是又是得瑟你上过太空这回事?
or just another reminder that you went to space?
人家觉得两不误嘛
A story can do two things.
唉 我觉得我都要得心脏病了
Ugh, I feel like I'm gonna have a heart attack.
你在制药公司工作...
You work in pharmaceuticals...
你觉得你能给他开个什么药不?
don't you have anything you can give him?
我只有新研制的利尿药
All I have is our new urine flow drug.
缓解他的焦虑没啥作用 不过药效很强 他尿尿的时候
Won't help with his anxiety, but it's so strong, when he pees
就会像装了个喷气包一样满屋子乱飞了
he'll fly around the room like he's got a jet pack.
这事一直在我脑子里转
I can't stop thinking about it.
你担心也没用啊
You know, worrying won't have any effect on what happens.
- 我知道  - 也许你可以做点实质性的事
- I know.  - Maybe you need to do something more productive.
好的
Okay.
啊
Ah.
假如我能准确投入
If I make this shot
那个垃圾桶
in the trash can,
说明探测器
the probe will have arrived
会完好无损到达
in perfect working order.
所以 你要不是疯了的话 你就是把你任务的命运
So, in addition to being crazy, you're resting the fate
投注在你的运动天分上
of the mission on your athletic prowess.
是的
Yes.
你能把你的健身脚踏车压坏
The man who crashed his stationary bike.
不是我压坏的 好吗?
I didn't crash it, okay?
我播放列表的歌节奏太快
My playlist was too up-tempo,
有点上头 所以摔下来了
I got light-headed and I fell off.
好了
Okay.
下面...
It all...
就是见证...
comes down...
奇迹的时刻
to this.
你高兴了吧? 现在可以放心了
You happy? Now you can relax.
你是哪门子科学家? 谁都知道
What kind of scientist are you? Everyone knows
得三投两中才行
you got to make two out of three.
也不算很惨
This isn't so bad.
对你来说是挺容易
That's easy for you to say.
你的椅子又没对着内衣区
Your chair's not facing the lingerie section.
天哪 怎么有那么多内裤
Boy, that's a lot of panties.
你们还舒服吗? 可能要等一会
You guys comfy? This might take a while.
我不懂为什么女人
You know, I don't understand why women
来买衣服
insist on making a big production
要这么大阵仗
out of buying clothes.
你说得对 我们应该和你一样
No, you're right, we should do what you do.
让我们的妈妈从休斯顿的沃尔玛寄裤子过来
Have our mom send us pants from the Walmart in Houston.
他们那有个人
They have a man there
知道我的个人风格
who understands my personal style.
等会见
Bye.
呃 我有个坏消息
Uh, I've got some bad news.
这里没有无线
There's no cell service in here.
哦
Oh.
好吧 没事
Well, that's all right.
智能手机发明之前
There were plenty of ways to pass the time
人们也有无数种方法消磨时间
before smart phones were invented.
说的没错
That's true.
我来拿手机查一下
I'll look them up.
特喵的
Son of a biscuit.
Sheldon 没事的
Sheldon, it's fine.
不 谁说没事
No, it's not fine.
哪门子21世纪的商场
What kind of store in the 21st century
连个无线都没有?
doesn't at least have Wi-Fi?
我要打给他们公司办公室...
I'm going to call their corporate office...
他喵了个咪的!
Son of a biscuit!
瞧好了 我的军队
Let's see, my armies
要从雄鹿地
are going to attack the Shire
去攻击夏尔
from Buckland.
我来扔骰子...
And I roll...
一个5 一个3
a five and a three.
好的
Okay.
我要防御 扔骰子...
And to defend, I roll...
两个6 我赢了
two sixes. I win.
天哪 又是两个六
Boy, double-sixes again.
要不是我亲眼见到
You know... if I hadn't seen it
我都难以置信
with my own eyes, I wouldn't believe it.
我想知道我们还要在这等多久
I wonder how long we're gonna be stuck here.
我不知道 但是她们为我们付出了好多
I don't know, but the girls do a lot for us.
至少这是我们能做的
It's the least we can do.
说得对 我觉得这才公平
Oh, that's true. I suppose it's only fair
我们互相妥协
we make compromises.
瞧你 这么成熟了
Look at you, being all mature.
我不明白你怎么这么惊讶
I don't know why you're so surprised.
和你住在一起这么多年 让我懂得了一件事
If there's one thing I know about after living with you
就是怎么妥协让步
for so many years, it's how to compromise.
等... 等一下?
I-I'm sorry?
你对我妥协让步?
You make compromises for me?
一直都是
All the time.
在这地球上?
On Earth?
在我们的生活里?
In our lives?
在...我们过的日子里?
That... That we're living?
是的 我...
Oh, yes. I...
就说昨天吧 午饭的时候 你的牙齿里卡了
Just yesterday, you had a-a big piece of lettuce
一片巨大的生菜
stuck in your teeth at lunch.
我说什么了吗? 没有
Did I say anything? No.
我妥协了
I compromised
把我的嘴巴闭得紧紧的
and kept my mouth shut.
你也应该这么做 因为当时所有人都在嘲笑你
Like you should've, because everyone was laughing at you.
那才不是妥协
That is not a compromise.
妥协是我开车送你去各种地方
A compromise is me driving you everywhere
因为你自己不愿意学车
because you refuse to learn how.
哦 我已经学会了 Amy教我的
Oh, I learned how. Amy taught me.
什么? 那... 那你为什么不开车?
What? Then... Then why don't you do it?
呃 因为开车很吓人
Uh, well, it's scary.
有时候我会把刹车和油门搞混
And sometimes I get the pedals mixed up.
但是 更重要的是 开车送我上班
But, more importantly, driving me to work
是你人生的意义所在
is one of the things that gives your life purpose.
我不能把它从你那里夺走
I can't take that away from you,
所以说... 我能做什么呢?
so... what do I do?
哦 拜托 我都快把答案告诉你了
Oh, come on, I'm practically feeding you the answer.
我妥协了
I compromise.
- 嘿 呃 谢谢你陪着我  - 我很乐意
- Hey, uh, thanks for keeping me company.  - I'm happy to.
我想出来走走对你有好处
I think getting out of the apartment will do you good.
那么... 我们去哪里?
So... where we headed?
如果你不介意的话 我想去寺庙
If it's okay with you, I'd like to go to temple.
兄弟 相信我 你不会想成为一个犹太教徒的
Buddy, trust me, you don't want to convert to Judaism.
我知道我表现得好像它很酷
I mean, I know I make it look cool,
但... 这也不是什么特别有趣的事
but... it's not all briskets and dreidels.
我是说去一个印度教的寺庙
I meant a Hindu temple.
哦 好吧
Oh. Okay.
那里不会像夺宝奇兵里演的那样 对吧?
It's not like Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom, right?
不会有什么拿着号角的光头把我的心脏撕裂吧
Some bald guy with horns isn't gonna rip my heart out.
哥们 那电影只是一些帝国主义的幻想
Dude, that movie's an imperialist fantasy
把如此一个美丽又和平的宗教的信徒
that makes the followers of a beautiful and peaceful religion
描绘成一群嗜血的野蛮人
look like a bunch of bloodthirsty barbarians.
你爱那个电影
You love that movie.
是啊 它是很好看
Yeah, it's pretty great.
看到你突然变得那么虔诚我有点吃惊
I'm surprised to see you suddenly get religious.
为什么?
Why?
呃 因为我已经认识你10年了
Well, because I've known you for ten years
你从来没有去过寺庙
and you've never gone to temple,
你从来没有谈过相信上帝
you never talked about believing in God,
上个光明节的时候我还看到你在一个巴西牛排屋
and last Diwali I watched you eat two pounds of sacred cow
吃了两磅的神牛肉
at a Brazilian steak house.
宗教是一件很私人的事情
Religion is a very personal thing.
我的确去寺庙... 我只是... 从来不谈这件事
I do go to temple... I just... I don't talk about it.
是啊 但是你是科学家
Yeah, but you're a scientist.
所以呢?
So?
所以说 作为一个科学家 你相信
So, as a scientist, you believe the way
理解宇宙要靠事实和证据
to understand the universe is through facts and evidence,
现在你指望
and now you're counting
一个全身蓝色
on some blue chick
三头六臂的妹子来帮你?
with a hundred arms to help you?
这太冒犯人了 你对印度教
That is so offensive. Does everything you know
的所有了解 都来自于夺宝奇兵吗?
about Hinduism come from Indiana Jones?
当然不是 还有辛普森一家
No. There's also Apu from The Simpsons.
好吧 很多的科学家都相信神灵
Well, lots of scientists believe in God.
好吗? 有牛顿 呃 法拉第
Okay? Newton, uh, Faraday,
呃 帕斯卡... 他们都是信徒
uh, Pascal... all were believers.
就算爱因斯坦也曾经攻击量子理论
Even Einstein was famous for attacking quantum theory
根据是"上帝不会靠掷色子
on the grounds that "God does not play dice
- 来控制宇宙  - 呃 他当然
- with the universe."  - Well, of course
相信上帝... 他和玛丽莲・梦露上床了
he believed in God... he slept with Marilyn Monroe.
其实这件事没有证据
Actually there's no proof of that.
你相信你的宗教 我相信我的
You believe in your religion, I'll believe in mine.
怎么样了?
How's it going in there?
呃
Eh.
这件衣服不太适合穿去上班
Not really a great outfit for work,
除非妓女和婊子部又有什么新的职位空缺
unless something opens up in the hookers and whores division.
- 嘿 我能问你一件事吗  - 当然可以
- Hey, can I ask you something?  - Sure.
我真的经常强迫你做一些你不想做的事吗?
Do I really force you to do things you don't want to?
是啊 但是没关系
Yeah, but it's okay.
怎么会没关系呢?
How is it okay?
我向自己保证过 如果我有朋友
I promised myself, if I ever got friends,
他们说什么我都会做
I'd do whatever they said.
真的 我很庆幸在遇到邪教之前遇到了你
Really, I'm lucky you found me before a cult did.
呃 那是很久之前的事了
Well, you know, that was a long time ago.
你现在已经是另一个女人了 你很聪明
You're a different woman now. You're smart,
你有很多好朋友 你还有一个男朋友
you've got great friends, you've got a boyfriend,
你很漂亮 你完全不懂时尚 但...
you're pretty, you have zero fashion sense, but...
总之 今晚我们做你想做的事
Anyway, tonight we're gonna do whatever you want.
真的吗?
Really?
当然 你说什么我们就做什么
Absolutely. You name it, we're doing it.
我们去手工艺博物馆织篮子
Basket weaving at the craft museum.
既然你已经说了
Well, you named it.
哦 还有一件事
Oh, here's another one.
我希望那些苹果煎饼粉放在橱柜的顶层隔板上
I wish that the apple pancake mix was on the top shelf
因为它的开头字母是A
because it starts with an "A,"
但我没有把它放在那里
but I don't put it there
因为我不希望你在为我做早饭的时候
because I don't want you breaking one of your little legs
把你可爱的小短腿给摔断了
when you're supposed to be making my breakfast.
现在轮到我来说 我做出的妥协了吗?
Is it my turn to talk about the compromises I make?
我还没说完 不过你说吧
I wasn't done, but go ahead.
他妥协地说道
He said, compromising.
因为你 我不能
Because of you, I'm not allowed
调节我自己家里的气温
to adjust the temperature in my own home.
我不能吹口哨
I'm not allowed to whistle.
我不能穿会发出声音的鞋子
I don't wear shoes that might squeak.
呃 你是一个物理学家 不是个马戏团的小丑
Well, you're a physicist, not a circus clown.
Sheldon 你没有意识到我因为你都没法和我爱的女人
Sheldon, do you realize I don't live with the woman I love
住在一起吗?
because of you?
没有别的原因 就是因为你
No other reason. Just you.
- 这是真的吗?  - 是啊 真的 上一次
- Is that true?  - Yes, it's true. The last time
我提起这件事的时候 你情绪崩溃
I brought it up, you had an emotional breakdown
跳上一辆火车逃跑了
and got on a train and ran away.
呃 考虑到我在这件事上的经历
Well, given my history on the subject,
现在提起它好像有点不顾后果
it seems a little reckless to bring it up now.
你完全无法想象你给你身边的人造成了
You have no idea how much you inconvenience
多少的不方便
the lives of everyone around you.
真是累死了!
It's exhausting!
你知道吗?
You know what?
你以为你那么宽容
You think you're so tolerant,
但事实是...
but the truth is...
你经常对我态度恶劣
you're mean to me a lot.
好吧 你以为
Yeah, you think
我注意不到那些讽刺我的评价
that I don't notice all those sarcastic comments
和你们的白眼 其实我注意到了 知道吗?
and those eye rolls, but I do. Hmm?
我的余光看得很远
I have excellent peripheral vision.
运气好 我都能看见我的耳朵
On a good day, I can see my ears.
Sheldon 我... 我很抱歉伤害到了你
Sheldon, I... I'm sorry if I hurt your feelings.
我只是忍这些忍得太久了
I've been holding a lot of this in for a while.
我也很抱歉 而且要是你想和Penny
Well, I'm sorry, too. And if you want
同居的话 我也没有意见
to live with Penny, then I think you should.
你真的同意了?
Do you mean that?
是啊 穿上你那双声音超大的鞋...
Yes. Yeah, just put on your squeaky shoes and...
离开我的生活吧
your way out of my life.
别这样 别难过啊
Come on, don't get upset.
我才没有难过
I'm not upset.
我只是在想象一个没有我最好的朋友的世界
I'm just imagining a world without my best friend in it.
哦 Sheldon
Sheldon.
没关系的
It's okay.
我... 我并不是要离开你的生活
I... I'm not leaving your world.
我只是说住到对门去而已
I'm just talking about living across the hall.
我懂的
I understand.
不管怎样 我希望你知道...
Either way, I want you to know that...
我明白自己是个多难缠的人
I'm aware of how difficult I can be.
所以我只想说...
So I just want to say...
谢谢你容忍我这么多年
thank you for putting up with me.
兄弟...
Buddy...
你们在这里待得怎么...?
How are you guys getting alo...?
什么情况? 怎么还哭了?
What? Why are there tears?
没事的
Everything's fine.
我们就是聊了聊搬家的事
We just started talking about living arrangements.
你疯了吗? 你明知道他想走就走
Are you crazy? You know he's a flight risk.
我是这么说的啊
That's exactly what I told him.
Sheldon 我们知道这个话题很敏感
Sheldon, we know this is a sensitive subject,
在你准备好之前 Leonard绝对不会搬走的
and Leonard's not gonna move out until you're ready.
好吧 你可以一点一点慢慢让我适应嘛?
Well, what if you did it gradually?
好啊...
All right. Well...
先从我一周和Penny住两天开始
how about we start with two nights a week
怎么样?
I live with Penny?
可不可以一周和她住一晚...
How about one night and...
但我让你吹口哨?
I let you whistle?
好吧
Okay.
而且得是我不在家的时候
When I'm not home.
听你的
You got it.
看到没
There we go,
又是我做了妥协
compromising again.
我们真是好室友
We really are the best.
就是这里啦
Here we go,
这是我第一次来印度教寺庙
my first Hindu temple.
你看见喷泉后面那座看起来像是
You see behind the fountain, that tower
金字塔的建筑了吗?
that looks like a pyramid?
那是希诃罗 象征着
It's called a Sikhara. It symbolizes
人类通往天堂的路
the connection between the human and the divine.
哦哦
Huh.
我还以为那是打小高尔夫球的地方呢
I always thought it was mini golf.
好了 我们下车吧?
All right. Shall we?
好啊 不过进去之前 有没有什么其他
Yeah. Just, uh, is there anything I should know
我需要注意的事情?
before I go in?
比如说?
Like what?
比如我穿成这样好吗?
Like am I dressed okay?
什么? 你去其他地方的时候
Really? So every other place you've been,
你都没觉得不好?
you thought this was fine?
我知道你现在压力很大
I know you're under a lot of pressure,
所以我就不跟你吵了
so I'm gonna let that pass.
抱歉 你说得对
Sorry. You're right.
我压力太大了
I'm so stressed.
但是你知道吗
But you know what,
每次我走进寺庙
whenever I walk into that temple
我都会觉得 无论发生什么 都没那么重要
I realize that whatever happens, it's okay.
我们是无限空间的一部分
We're all part of an immense pattern,
尽管我们无法理解它 我们却很开心
and though we can't understand it, we can be happy to know
这个空间的运行也依赖着我们
that it's... it's working its will through us.
这样也很好
That's nice.
无论你说是上帝还是宇宙还是个体
Whether you call it God or the universe or the self,
我们都是互相联系的 这样很好...
we're all interconnected, and that's just a beautiful...
混蛋! 那货刚碰了我车!
Son of a bitch! That guy just dinged my car!
你... 你想什么呢?
S... Seriously?
你... 你就打算这么开走嘛?
Y... You were just gonna drive away?
就像我的生活
Like my life
还不够惨似的
isn't hard enough right now.
一个宇宙探测器可能会毁掉
A space probe might be destroyed,
我父母正在撕破脸离婚
my parents are going through an awful divorce,
给我的狗狗剃毛的人给它剪了个刘海!
the guy who cuts my dog's hair just gave her bangs!
嘿 Raj
Raj.
你也看见了 她就像阿呆与阿瓜里面的金凯利!
You saw her. She looks like Jim Carrey from Dumb and Dumber!
Raj 你有条短信
Raj, you just got a text.
探测器开启了 一切顺利
The probe turned on. It's fine.
哦 太好了
Oh, good.
合十礼 爷爷您好
Namaste, Grandpa.
我还以为这会很无聊呢
I thought this was gonna be boring,
不过好像还挺好玩的
but it's actually kind of fun.
别跟Amy说 不过咱们以后每周日都得来了
Don't tell Amy that. We'll be here every Sunday.
Sheldon 这个篮子编的真好
Sheldon, that really is an excellent basket.
这不是篮子
It's not a basket.
这是十六世纪中国士兵戴的头盔
It's a soldier's helmet from 16th century China.
真好
Very nice.
是啊 看起来棒呆了
Yeah, it looks great.
我看见你的表情了
I saw that.
虽然一周只能和你做一天室友
Well, roomie, it's only one night a week,
不过这也是个很好的开始啦
but it's a start.
我知道 我真的觉得Sheldon很棒
I know. I'm really proud of Sheldon.
是啊 我也这么觉得
Yeah, I'm proud of him, too.
你们能小点声吗? 屋里有人
Can you keep it down? Some of us
要睡觉了
are trying to sleep out here.